we're going to go ahead and get started.
This is Brian Douglas.
He is here to talk to you about training AI on your own code.
I am going to be listening intently because I would like to know do this
round of applause for Brian.
All right.
I gifted you light mode.
All right. Good morning.
I'm Brian Douglas.
I go by bdougie on the internet.
You might know me from the internet. I used to work at GitHub for about five years.
I've been on their content and stuff like that for a long time,
but as of recent, I started this new company called Paper Compute.
I have nothing to sell you.
I'm just here to talk about some open source stuff
that we've been doing in the last couple of months.
And really, if you guys talk to us about the at the booth.
So we have a booth upstairs in the expo hall,
you kind of got
the earliest version of this and I'll go through some other details.
So this should be a speedrun.
This is not a workshop so don't expect to like step one.
Step two, step three.
I'm going to just share my journey of how I learned this.
I'm more than happy to talk.
I actually have a blog post on this that has step one. Step two.
At first step three.
But I'll show that later. Cool.
I'll start with Pokémon, so who knows what Pokémon is.
Okay, excellent. So I'm an elder millennial.
This came out when I was a kid on the Game Boy.
It was a big deal.
I spent a lot of time playing Pokémon Red, and I will show you
this all makes sense eventually, but I'm going to show you
how speedrun Pokémon and how I sort of navigated that.
And it's kind of led into sort of training AI in your code. So
actually it also preferences.
This also banned me from Claude as well.
So use at your own discretion.
So in case study there's a Pokémon game on the Game Boy,
Pokémon Red. I read a paper and I'll talk about this paper in a second.
But I wanted to be able to like test out
some of the stuff we were building an open source.
One of the things, particularly if you went up at the booth,
takes tapes on dev, is a way to capture agent sessions,
and I wanted to basically validate the stuff that we're doing at scale.
So like an intense amount of scale.
So the idea here is I wanted to basically speedrun Pokémon to capture a thousand
turns per session, and then each session is basically an epic.
And then every time I ran into recession, I would actually capture that data
and then go learn.
That's what starts to tell him. Loop.
So one of the actually processes, because actually leads
into a bunch of stuff that was going to talk about soon.
But the idea here is that we have these two things that paper compute
open source get get up repo.
Once tapes.dev, we spend a lot of time upstairs
talking about turning your agent tokens into skills using tape sessions.
But the thing we didn't really talk about was Stereo and Stereo.
We're not really chatting about here at the conference,
because if you're interested and you have that problem
like we can we can talk to you about it.
But most folks are really just like running agents on their own MacBook.
Or if you're really, really skilled, you're probably using a cloud environment
or a sandbox.
But like, we're all kind of this learning.
We're pretty early around the trajectory of the curve and inflection.
But Stereo, it's it's a runtime for agents.
So like a sandbox but actually batteries included.
Cool.
So disclaimer I'd mentioned this earlier when I started,
I have nothing to sell you.
This all stuff that I opened that's been open source within our organization.
So the only way you can pay us is through a five star rating in the review.
I don't know if we're doing reviews said this event, but I'd appreciate that.
Oh, we are excited.
Well, there we go.
Bottles of water at the at the end.
So this is a setup that I have for Pokemon.
Again, bear with me as I explain this because it all connects.
Pokemon is a game you start as a kid in your house, you wake up late
and you have to go to Professor Oak's lab to get your first Pokemon.
So I thought, hey, if I could like use a couple things.
So PyGameBoy, which I didn't actually explain a couple slides ago,
but PyGameBoy is a python library that you can play Gameboy ambulatory game.
So if you if you want to go deep in the lower, like you can have ROMs.
These are games that have been flashed that you can
then play on handheld devices or on your computer.
And with PyGameBoy you can play any game or game headless.
So meaning I don't have to watch it play.
I could just let it run like through an agent.
So then that kind of unbox and I'm like, cool.
Well, I can use Claude Code or Codex to basically run PyGameBoy
because Claude Code is just a harness because it says code.
But it's really it's a
it's a pretty general purpose harness that you can do almost anything with.
So I ended up doing this in a sense of like,
I knew I wanted to run the agent 1000 turns,
but I also wouldn't record those sessions and identify the learning patterns.
And then every time, if I got blocked or if I hit a,
I couldn't get over a bridge that would get recorded.
So this is actually live.
This is actually screenshots of the game playing.
So what I did is every ten turns take a screenshot.
So that way the agent can always go back and learn and find out what happened.
So when you get blocked you can identify this thing is like that.
This character is not quite getting to conclusion.
And my only conclusion was to Pokemon.
So it's a very beginning of the game. You start.
Can I get to Professor Oak's lab?
There's no battling, there's no conflict.
It just get there, pick a Pokemon.
And it's wanted to get to that point.
But the challenge is
I ran this like for hours and would not basically get to anything.
When I found out
is I forgot to tell the agent to talk to people in the game,
because one of the first context
clues in the game is talk to your mom,
and your mom will tell you exactly where to go, but an agent would have no idea.
So one of the rules actually had is I can't use the internet to go under
and how to play Pokemon.
It has to be self learned within the ecosystem that I'm giving it the plan.
So the agent was
it wasn't learning, it was just politely hallucinating progress.
I would actually celebrate wins of like, hey, we finished thousand turns.
We did it absolutely right.
You guys know that from Claude.
It would basically just do this and this is back in February.
So yeah, this would have been like five for Codex and like one of the opens. But
what I'm
getting at is like this was like a nice construct
for me to take that context and go serve it back to Asia.
So a lot of folks we talked to upstairs to like,
they have a skill where they kind of sit and look at their sessions
at the end of the week,
and then they summarize, like stuff that's been done, good for you.
That's great.
But you're definitely like top notch when it comes to like using agents.
But I don't do that.
So instead I just dump all the context into a tape database.
So time we were using SQLite,
we've actually moved on to Postgres for limitation reasons.
SQLite has single single player methodologies.
Only one person can write to the database.
This setup was actually ten Pokémon agents running simultaneously,
1000 turns each and learning it's constantly piggyback. So.
So I have the tapes database which all the raw data.
So this is the log for agents.
And then I have this memory folder that I
this is concept with from master over to blog post from observational memory.
And this is like taking your 1000 sessions and then writing an observation.
So think about the end of the day.
You open up your journey like, man, I saw this amazing
talk from Brian Douglas from San Francisco, California.
It was amazing.
He had a great shirt on his glasses.
I'm just kidding.
I don't know if you did this that the other day,
but these are observations at the end of your sessions.
I was just dropping these embarked on.
So if these get written by the agent, the agent gets me human readable feedback.
So things like when I found out, oh, the NPC has no idea.
We've not talked to any NPC.
We have no context of the awareness of the entire world.
We should build that into the into the loop.
And then I also have this observer state.
Jason, this is something I actually discovered later.
And this is very specific.
Pokemon like this could leave something different in your code base.
If you're approaching this and I'll show you how to do that.
But it's like up, down, left, right.
So like you go up to you go out one.
The things actually worked with the observer
is that when you go through a door, it takes seven seconds for a cooldown
because you can't stand back and forth through caves if everybody's playing
JRPGs or any sort of games. No.
Yes. No. Yeah.
So, like, you just can't stand back and forth and like, refresh and like, go
like level up and kill a bunch of enemies that way.
So that was something actually learned through the observer MD
as I was like looking at the doc and then chat with the agent and say, hey.
Okay, well, we got here. What's happening?
What do you think? Like, what's this chat through?
I do like Socratic method to get out of that that that loop.
So this kind of concludes the Pokemon section of this this talk.
But this is all live on Pokemon Kafka.
I actually did have ten simultaneous agents also record
through Kafka and then capture anomaly detection.
So a lot of the anomalies like not going through doors.
Actually, when I got to the point of battling,
that was like
some weird anomalies of like, okay, when you're below a certain HP,
you should probably eat a berry or you should probably switch Pokemon.
There's like this a lot of nuance that I had to have the agent learn about
the game, and I guess I'm looking at me like, man, Pokemon this too much.
But the goal was I ended up getting to the point where I could even,
like, viciously get a self-healing infrastructure loop
to eventually get the three seconds of Pokemon.
So game starts, spam the A button, and then A is the name of the character.
A is the name of the Pokemon, and the speed runs to get the Pokemon
for Professor Oak. But at that point there the observer.
I ended up figuring out that you don't hit A when you pick your Pokemon yet
be because he asks you yes or no, and he had it be to get out of that that.
So it's just a lot of like nuance.
But again, we think about our code bases, thinks about stuff we've been shipping
for like 15 or 20 years, maybe less than that five years.
There's a lot of nuance that we know about our code base.
Or maybe we have learned in complexity that we've created the code
base that you kind of learn on the fly.
But lately we've been basically this, like shoot from the hip and it's like
we've got new every five hours. You get a refreshing cloud session.
So we're just going live next.
Like we got refreshed, we got more token window.
Let's go.
But we never learned from the last five hours of sessions.
And that's what kind of leads me into this like brute force discovery
and like massive learning.
So it's a great way to understand a code base to go search and grep,
identify files that you should be understanding things like writing a blog,
like I like writing blog post about code bases.
I don't know, it's one of the the more fun investing things
that I've been doing.
And it's
mainly I'm not going to write this code, but I do need to know how this code works
and you know how to navigate this and discuss it with engineers.
So what I ended up developing is like a cheap simulator
to identify some of these best practices that are coming out of his papers
and stuff like that.
So I encourage you like it's open source, like take this, run with it.
If not, go play a different game.
But what I'm what I'm getting at is like, we are now in a place where
we're all leveraging AI.
We're all here in this conference, like, you didn't pay for a ticket
because you were using AI, or if you're not using like
probably sign up today and then catch up and one of the workshops.
But Cloud Code stores your sessions, codec searches,
sessions on your routine for 30 days after 30 days is deleted.
So as I walked through all this like Pokemon navigation of like infrastructure
and learning
like all those sessions
are also on my machine from because they use Claude Code as my harness.
But the value is all being lost because we're just moving on
to the next five hours
and like the next window, or the next day, or the next month, we pay the next $200.
I guess you paid 180 pound.
Is that what the price is that convert that right.
But what I'm getting at is like, we're paying for this
and we're just renting the tokens and then we get no output from it.
So there's a lot of opportunity for us to figure this out.
So all the Pokemon turned into what I call super agent.
So Super Agent, I thought it would be funny to say that out loud.
Sweeper agent, but it goes through code base in this sweeps through.
So I had a bunch of code that I shipped last summer
when I was five coding and I never touched ever again.
So I've got a lot of the garbage code.
What if I went through
and like this lint in it and like massively fixed a bunch of stuff?
Or what if I ended up like setting up like ten
parallel agents to write documentation or create a context like a bunch of
spectrum and developing context that that's engineer can figure this out.
So that's what Super agent is.
And it basically takes V,
I separate VMs, which is Stereo where I talked about earlier.
But then also each VM has a tape session being recorded.
So then I have like now ten tape sessions of data that I can now have
to one generate skills but also generate documentation, generate context.
I'll get to about fine tuning a model.
But this is a massive amount of data.
And if you're working in enterprise or a company
and like you're paying for the stuff, you should be extracting value.
I know some people are in a position where their company is pacifically.
They have ideal where their data is being trained by Anthropic.
So you get a huge discount.
But if you want to give the data to Anthropic, but if you want to give the data
Anthropic — they'll give you a discount.
But that's expensive. That's really good to go.
Cursor currently is in a deal for $10 billion at minimum with space
like that's the high point.
I've actually been working with a lot of AI companies in the last few years.
People are selling your data.
So using I don't want to name a bunch of companies,
but like they are selling the data is expensive.
So you should you should quit for yourself and you should do something with that.
So that's what I'm here to say.
So sweeper is also open source.
If you're interested in taking a look,
there's a blog post on both the Pokémon and the super agent stuff.
Highly recommend this. Take a look at it.
The one thing I would also say is like the agents,
they don't always need a bandit model.
So like we've got Opus 4.8 as of like two days ago.
That's great.
It's working pretty well.
It's better than 4.7, apparently.
Maybe, I don't know, who knows.
We're past performance is not particularly for future growth, but
sometimes you could use the cheaper model for certain things.
Like when I talk about super agent IPS haiku at scale
with ten different agents, and I can crush that because it's
a very bespoke like rudimentary up down, left right type experience.
So now I have an opportunity to use a cheaper model
and have to get the job done.
Maybe it takes longer, but like if we're using backward agents to run this stuff
over the weekend, overnight like none the wiser. So.
So this is I feel like a really good image.
But like at paper compute, like we capture traces.
And the beauty of this if you ever like, I took your school book and wrote
a little picture on the bottom corner and like,
had like little stickman and you like, fold it like you
kind of trace back and forth and you had this cartoon like,
this is kind of what we're doing with all of our sessions.
Like, we we figure things out.
We've like innovated something, whether we wrote the code
or the agent or the code, we've innovated something that we should keep
as a novel concept of like we should share and transfer that knowledge.
And I also want to mention that I was exploring this couple of months ago,
the same week that I finished the Pokemon thing is the same week that the auto
research repo dropped, so everything I explained is basically this.
Karpathy has a repo about our research.
Qwen3, has auto research built into the open-source model.
So it's a concept of self-healing.
And the self-healing infrastructure
exists already in a Chinese model today from Alibaba.
So I sell this because I dig an unlocked from Claude.
So as remind you that Claude didn't block my account for running ten parallel
super agents.
Turns out if you run a blog post and emailed them and say, hey,
sorry about that, I was actually running with sleeper agent.
I had an old repo.
I ended up fixing it in less than an hour.
I fixed all lint errors that I was avoiding for years.
This is a project, has about 100 users on it and I get
this didn't happen but couldn't be bothered to fix this project.
But I was able to run a super agent to clean it up and bring it up to modern
standard times six months later because it's a six month old product.
So this is like kind of like where we're thinking about with tapes
like their opportunity for collecting the trace status, but anomaly detection.
So now we detect is like, hey, ten tool falls have failures like what happened.
But another anomaly is actually a success.
So if you have 26 skills in locations out of like
ten sessions, like there's probably something good happening there.
And a lot of us, we're not even like looking with the fine,
fine tuned from of identifying anything of value.
Like we're kind of like, again, we're shooting for the head.
We're like, cool, prompt me, no mistakes, clean code, go.
And there's a lot of stuff we can learn for.
Even if a simple prop like that, there's a lot we can learn from that one prompt.
So that's why it's important to keep these trace sessions.
They unblock me after the blog post took about 12 hours.
Pretty amazing.
It's all robots that answer your emails, but apparently
the blog post was good about.
So we've been upstairs talking about this.
The story about turning a dead tokens of skills.
If you haven't quite got this concept yet and I haven't explained,
this is like, again, you're you're using tokens, you get a five hour window
for every time you get a new refresh, like access to tokens.
You get a weekly allowance of tokens.
Despite the fact that you're paying for this thing,
you get no allowance and you could pay for extra time and for pastime.
So even for situations, you're like, man, should I turn on Claude Code fast?
Or should I pay for overages like this?
This is the value there.
There's a lot of opportunity to have to stand that just by looking at the data.
So I want to talk about this tape skills pipeline.
And I'll get to the fine tuning story in a second.
So to wind this down but takes quite the session to generate
skills, a lot of folks asked us like how this works.
So my co-founder back is actually the one that designed all this stuff.
But we have like a Merkle DAG.
So you know, get every git commits sits
within a Dag so you can go and have a hash for every commitment.
And they have like these branches and link looks like this.
So every session has turns I talk about
a thousand turns within a session for like my Pokemon experience.
But it's the same thing for your session.
So every time you talk type Claude, Codex, whatever, that's your session.
Your session has begun.
Claude is a little weird where they start splintering sessions in a weird way,
and then we'll figure out how to display that in an observable way eventually.
But this consider this very, very dimensionally.
Each session you type, Claude, that's your session.
When you do clear, that's a new session.
When you close it, you start again.
That's a new session.
So once you have the concept of I pull, everything I've said in
this session is now stored in a trace.
Now you can do some cool things of like I've got the skill called check the tapes.
So again data storage machine for 30 days.
I can go back six months and say check the tapes.
Like how did we get here? Like, why did this happen?
We can get blame, but who's who's actually using good blame?
Cool.
Okay. What were you doing? Good point.
Sorry, I apologize, but I don't get blamed.
I happen to use get blame in, like, six months because I've been building
a bunch of tools that look like get blame that perform much better.
I built a tool called On Top of Landscape called Git Blame,
and it's just basically this.
It was very kind of blog post on it, but it wasn't great.
So I don't use it anymore.
But if I can check the tapes and say, hey, give me all the sessions that I like,
solve the door, cool down window for Pokemon.
Like how do we how do we like turn that into a story?
What I did actually recently is I built entire wireframe
of our actual cloud product and we have a designer,
came one in the contract, and she's like, hey, can you share your prompts with me?
And I'm like, I don't have my prompts.
Like, who saves her prompts? Copy and paste.
You don't want to see my problems,
but I had the tapes so I could say, hey, based on these wireframe, let's open up
GitHub issues for every single feature and then every feature has the prompt.
It has the intent, it has a token usage, it has all the
quality of that insider would need to then go take to design the product.
And I've had a very, very rudimentary wireframe.
I've run a developer by trade, but I sort of shattered science
prompt coded that thing the like to
was but having a skill that's called check the tapes.
I can go look at deeper into the database.
And the way this works is also
you have like all these sessions that have been charted and we have
we well,
I say currently we're not labeling the data right now, but
at the time we were doing this for tape SQL light, we were labeling the data.
So I can have actually have labeled data of like this is type firm and stuff.
This is a design stuff, which was super helpful.
What I'm showing
briefly for folks who asked enough questions upstairs is tapes deck.
So Tapes deck was like we had to open source.
There's no no sign up.
This is all built on the command line.
And you can actually have a visualization observability of your tape sessions.
This is why it's called
tape deck and tapes to being the most durable form of media.
So that I can see all my sessions and then I can sort of click in
and then see all the input output tokens, all the prompts,
like it's all the raw data.
And I think a lot of folks
have asked a question about, well, what if my prompt has sensitive
information, like what if you didn't put sensitive information in your prompts?
But this is all on you.
So like this is all your data and this is all the data on your machine.
So like how you treat that data and how you sanitize it, I guess
it's open for discussion and open source.
But like for now it's all pretty raw data.
So put secrets in your code but we'll get there.
So yeah this is like this is looking at the every single.
So it's hard to see.
But these are all tool calls these like cogs.
And every pencil is a skill invocation.
So like this is you can actually visualize
like how often skills are being called
and how often tool calls are being leveraged.
And this is actually
documented in our sorry tape stack is documented
our documentation and tapes dev takes skill is a feature that we haven't really.
We have a one blog post on it.
We have spent a lot of time talking about it
until here at this conference, but because we have everything
stored in a database, I didn't mention it's also a vector eyes as well.
So you can do natural language.
You could say tape search whatever string of text you're looking for,
and it will bring all the sessions up of that search.
So if you want to take that session, the output of all the sessions
that you've searched and say, hey, create a skill.
So this you could do with like a small model I've actually been using.
I'm a bit of a I'm a cheap person, so I've been using for as my main driver
for models because it's a year old and it's super cheap,
but you can generate a pretty decent skill like first pass.
I do recommend that you do what a human to like, go clean up like the skill itself
and like go read it as a human with your human eyes
and then identify if and actually you leverage.
But once the skill is up, the skill works, it gets invoked.
Then you can be used to tape sessions and identify
how often it gets invoked and whether it's working.
And then
I guess you could probably get to a point where you use Tesla
to identify a scorecard or whether the skill is actually useful,
which I love to talk to the Tesla people about that next.
But I say all this because I moved it to eventually we have skills,
and now I want to get on this path of like, what if I train the model?
I had the benefit of working in this company called continue
retrain the model called next edit.
So back when tab completion was still cool,
we had a model that we trained using specialized fine tuning.
It's the exact same way that Cursor Composer two has fine tuned on your data.
So if you're a pro user of cursor, congratulations!
Your data is now being sold to space.
But that same pattern is basically what I'll show you in a sense.
So this is the blog post I wrote about this,
and this will have more detail what I'm about to go to.
But I had 77,000 tape sessions, so this is me
just starting the record as of January and everything,
every single thing that I wrote, I was just recording an empty database.
And what's super cool about this is like, we're we're in London, right?
This is like the home of Pink Floyd and Rolling Stones and the Beatles.
Did I get all that? Right? Okay,
yeah.
But anyway, like what I, what?
I play music and whatever I like about the Beatles around
this time is like they actually intently use less tracks.
They act like they get everyone in the room and they just play live.
And it's like, I, I never grew up.
My point listen to the Beatles or anything like that until I got older.
But it's got like a weird, like deep rabbit hole about this.
But sometimes you can just do more with less.
But right now I have a lot.
So 77,000 tape sessions a lot.
It's about four gigs worth of data.
We're doing about a gig of data a week.
So if you're storing sessions on your machine, you have about four gigs.
If you want to push that up to a year, you're probably like approaching
50 to 100 gigs of this data
that's sitting on your machine that you've never looked at.
And maybe a handful of us are chatting with on Fridays.
So the way I'm going to explain this is two different ways
specialize, fine tuning. We're not going to go super deep.
I'm going to mention some term go, go, go and read papers later.
But specialized fine tuning is the process that cursor used for composer to DPO,
which is direct preference optimization is a bit more specific
and we all just break this down.
QLoRA is the tool that folks would probably use PyTorch or Unsloth
with.
And you can fine tune again on your own data and essentially do this.
So if you think about model like a book.
So every model is a book.
It's got lots and lots of information.
Be like co-located into a place.
This is why you can search for Pokémon
and search for like good restaurants in the same chat session.
Specialized fine tuning
as if you were to write your skill in the margins of the book.
So you're now adding extra context and extra notes into the book.
Does that kind of make sense to you all? Cool.
So if you go, I don't know.
I don't write a lot of notes in my book.
I haven't been in school in a long time, so like none the wiser, I actually did.
Kind of annoyed when I get a used book and it has a bunch of random notes.
I'm like, who is this person? Why is this here?
Maybe they were famous, I don't know, but that specialized
fine tuning and what I ended up doing is taking Qwen 4B.
So it's a very it's a smaller model.
And I kind got the idea of what if I embed the skill
into a small language model and the results are actually really good.
So I'd say about I didn't spend a lot of time,
I didn't have a lot of data, and there's all my skills.
Actually. This was my all my skills.
This was me and three other team members skills, and I was able to embed
the skill into the model.
Now, you're not the question.
It's like, why would you embed in the model?
And why would you not just use a skill and invoke that harness?
And I would say, why not?
And I was really just going down this near
tonight moment of like, I'm just going to test it out.
It's great work.
It actually works pretty decently for a small language
language model on your MacBook or on your or whatever.
Your Linux machine works pretty good.
So think about the use case for.
This is like it is the Pokémon use case.
It is onboarding to a random project. It's
onboarding into some random documentation that you have to go slog through.
It's a very, very specialized small language model problem.
It is not your daily driver.
So like if you're trying to replace Claude Code, you will not.
If you're trying to get Sonnet equivalent interactions, you will not.
But if you're just trying to prove a point and do a cool thing for something
that's very bespoke, if you're working on a machinery
or you're working with like weird languages that have the spokes, situations
like memory management, like this is an approach.
And I've talked to a couple of enterprises who are approaching it in this manner.
I will mention the DPO, which is reinforcement learning from preferences,
which kind of looks like
if you have two choices, it always pick the best choice no matter what.
So this is actually really expensive and I'll just get that out of the way.
I don't recommend doing this ever,
unless you're a researcher and you work at meta.
I don't know if that guy's here, but like
this is probably a thing that costs a lot of money, that you have
a very expensive problem for that you have.
Yeah, you've got reasons to use this.
And I say this because I was actually doing this all on a 40, 70.
So gaming rig specialized time tuning works perfect.
This could not run. It needed 24GB of Vram.
I had no sorry, I need 32. I had 24.
So I had to upgrade my I upgrade to a 32 gigabyte 50.
90, which I shamelessly did.
And the results were basically middling.
So lucky enough, I actually got a friend who was at Nvidia.
I will not name their name, but I did get some H1 hundreds and sorry.
The other thing I was mentioned is it's like cliff notes.
So if anybody use Cliff notes, is everything here in
just drop outs?
We use those things.
So Cliff notes, if I explain this, this is the book
you get instead of reading the actual college textbook.
So you will get the cliff note and then you'll take the test.
Not recommended.
But it's like if you just want to skip the line until like
just take the test and learn the cliff notes.
So that's what DPO is.
That's fascinating. This culture culture shock here.
This is why university costs so much in the US because we cheat.
So results DPO on a 4 billion parameter.
Not good.
Not even worth it.
Don't even try going to be like an expensive
like you're probably spend $1,000 a week and compute just to get something
that doesn't work on a 7 billion parameter model.
Yeah, go for it. But also very expensive.
So I actually was just doing this because I had this talk
and I wanted to like kind of round up this talk into a conclusion.
But what I'm doing next is I'm actually meeting with folks
who actually know how to do research, and we'll figure this out together.
But this is more of a side project quest for me.
So with that said DPO.
All right, all right, all right.
All it does is pick the right selection every single time.
All the time.
Anybody watch this movie?
It's this American culture thing.
Just the American in the back.
All right.
Matthew McConaughey, one of his earliest movies.
It's a quote to me.
So basically I'll wrap this up is like step one is captured sessions.
Like, if you leave this room today, go look at Claude
sessions and start using them.
If you want to like the data and pull it off your machine tape
dev, it's open source.
Definitely leverage it. But the next step is the next step isn't much different.
So the best part about this is multiplayer coding sessions.
So multiplayer as in the sense of you're all solo player on your machine global.
If you have a second machine, you're probably not transmitted
data back and forth, like what's get to the point
where we actually transfer that knowledge
that transmit the knowledge actually looks like skills.
It's probably the best way to do this.
And then you now move into a place where you can unlock model freedom.
So like if you're using Claude Code and you want to use Codex
because Codex turns out to be better this week, you can just
transfer the skills of the Codex or Pi coder or anything else.
But we have the option.
We have optionality to do this.
I know as of today and properties Anthropic
IPO in the next couple of months, it's announced their SEC filing.
I'm going to read it on the plane ride home.
My background is finance. I went to school for finance.
So that's my my guilty pleasure is auditing SEC filings.
But the next thing is model choice.
Like at that point you don't need this all the time.
You can use haiku,
you can use some random Chinese model like that's an opportunity.
And then eventually we'll start.
The other shoe will drop drop.
And we'll have to think about cost.
So trace the data reinforced with learnings.
Find us in Expo hall.
That is me on and I think I have that slide.
This is me on the other hand. Thank you.
Thank you so much, Brian.
We have one minute anyone has a rapid fire questions
Brian.
Everyone thinks yeah just work for Codex.
It's just cool code.
Yeah it's a great question.
So today we're for it does not work for Codex.
It worked at a moment but things change quickly.
So we currently today worked for Cloud Code Conductor in Omaha.
We're more than happy to make it work for Codex
is someone needs to say they need it.
That's pretty much the only limitation.
That is all the time we have.
I'm so sorry, but Brian. I'll be.
Outside is at his booth as well.
So catch him, ask him questions.
Hunt him down. He'll be here all day.
Thank you guys so much.
We now have a coffee break. And like I said at the